https://www.whsfa.org/privacy-policy/

Twitter
Home Shop FAQs Login 0 Items Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy (the "Policy") explains how information is collected, used and disclosed by Wisconsin High School Forensic Association (WHSFA), with respect to your access and use of whsfa.org’s services, whether through our website (located at whsfa.org), third party sites (outlined below), or social networking services (Facebook, Twitter, Google, YouTube, LinkedIn), (together referred to below as "Wisconsin High School Forensic Association," or the "Service").What Information Do We Collect?We collect certain information when you connect to or use whsfa.org or wisconsinspeech.org in various ways. This information may be information that can identify you as a person or non-personal information and is either collected automatically or as a result of your specific input of the information. All information collected in any way is referred to collectively in this Policy as "Information." All Information is currently processed and stored in the United States on either Wisconsin High School Forensic Association’s servers, or the servers of the third party sites and services noted in the following section.Third Party Sites and ServicesWHSFA utilizes the following third-party services to carry out our business operations:Kinsta (whsfa.org web hosting)Google G Suite (email, document/data storage and collaboration)Arcstone AMO Association Management Online (membership/dues management and communication)Intuit QuickBooks (financial accounting management)SpeechWire.com (interscholastic contest registration and operations)Dialpad (telephone telecommunications management)MailChimp (email newsletter and marketing)Moosend (email newsletter and marketing)XPS Ship (shipping/mailing)Website Visit/CookiesWe automatically collect information when you visit our websites. We collect your IP address and browser header (version and type of browser) in a log file. We also collect your Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks.We may also automatically collect certain Information through the use of "cookies" or web beacons. These are small files that your browser places on your computer. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the websites, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our websites, and to improve our Service.Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.You may click on the following links: http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ for information on how to opt-out of the use of cookies or Web beacons.Sign Up/InstallYou are required to provide the following information to Wisconsin High School Forensic Association when you sign up for the Services: your email address, your username, your name in real life, your high school/organization and its address and phone numbers; other information is voluntary, including, but not limited to: your interests and your picture (for your profile). We automatically collect the time you connect ("timestamp"). Also, if you sign up via an ad click, we automatically collect your device type and unique device identifier.LoginWe collect the following information when you log in to Wisconsin High School Forensic Association: your geographic location (specified by latitude and longitude) and your IP address. These are collected automatically as part of the login process as a security precaution to help safeguard identity.How Do We Use the Information We Collect?We use Information for the following purposes:to administer our websites and provide our services or information you requestto process and complete any transactions;to promote Wisconsin High School Forensic Association in general;to respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests, and complaints and provide customer service;to track visitor movement and activity in the aggregate (for example, to give us information about what parts of the websites users are visiting)to personalize and improve Wisconsin High School Forensic Association services and features and your experiences when you use Wisconsin High School Forensic Association, such as providing content or features that match your profile, location or interests;to send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, our services;help prevent fraud or other misuse; andfor any other stated purpose for which the Information was collected.In addition, we may use your email address to send you emails for both transactional (e.g., confirmation of or issues with Services) and promotional purposes (e.g., newsletters, new product offerings, special discounts, event notifications and third-party offers). Email messages we send to you may contain code that enables our database to track your usage of the emails, including whether the email was opened and what links (if any) were clicked. If you would rather not receive promotional emails from us, please see the section in each email labeled "Choice/Opt-Out".With Whom Do We Share Your Information?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be utilized for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Specificallywith analytics providers for the purpose of analyzing user data;with service providers who are working with us in connection with the operation of our site or our services;anonymous or aggregate data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes;when you give us your consent to do so;when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants or court orders;to enforce or apply our privacy policy, our terms of use or our other policies or agreements;to protect the rights, property, or safety of Wisconsin High School Forensic Association, our users, or others; andin connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of organization assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where personal information may be disclosed or transferred as one of our assets.How Do We Use Your Information for Analytics?We may allow analytics providers to collect your Information within the Service and they may share it with us.Links to Other SitesWisconsin High School Forensic Association may contain links to other sites and apps, including in advertisements. Any information you provide on those sites is provided directly to the owner of that site and is subject to that party's privacy policy. Our privacy policy does not apply to such sites, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of those sites.What Steps Do We Take To Protect Your Information?While we take measures to protect your Information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration, despite our efforts, no security measures are impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse.Accessing and Modifying Your InformationIf you have an account, you can access and modify certain Information that you provided to us that is associated with your account by logging in and editing your profile information on Wisconsin High School Forensic Association request modifications to any Information that you cannot edit via the Service, please contact Wisconsin High School Forensic Association’s user support at office@whsfa.orgOpting OutYou may "opt out" of receiving marketing or promotional emails and push notifications from us by changing your account preferences or by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out of these messages, you will still receive emails from us, about your account, our services and other pertinent information related to our services. These communications are considered part of the service and your account, which you cannot opt-out from receiving.Deactivating Your Account and Deleting Account InformationYou can deactivate or permanently delete your account by contacting our office at office@whsfa.org. Deactivating your account lets you remove your profile without permanently deleting it. We reserve the right, but are not required, to permanently delete your Information if you do not reactivate your account within 60 days of deactivation. We will then delete all of your account Information.International UsersIf you are located outside the United States, please note that we may transfer your Information to the United States (or any other country in which we operate) and process it there. By using Wisconsin High School Forensic Association, you consent to the collection, transfer, use, storage and disclosure of your Information as described in this Policy.Our Policy Toward ChildrenOur online services are not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal Information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected personal Information of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete such Information from our files as soon as possible.Your California Privacy RightsBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by editing their profile.Disclosure to Protect Abuse VictimsNotwithstanding any other provision of this Policy, Wisconsin High School Forensic Association reserves the right, but has no obligation, to disclose any Information that you submit to Wisconsin High School Forensic Association, if in its sole opinion, Wisconsin High School Forensic Association suspects or has reason to suspect, that the Information involves a party who may be the victim of abuse in any form. Abuse may include, without limitation, elder abuse, child abuse, spousal abuse, neglect, or domestic violence. Information may be disclosed to authorities that Wisconsin High School Forensic Association, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate to handle such disclosure. Appropriate authorities may include, without limitation, law enforcement agencies, child protection agencies, or court officials.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to the PolicyAny Information that is collected is subject to the Policy in effect at the time such Information is collected. We may, however, modify the Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes to this Policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on Wisconsin High School Forensic Association or by sending you an email or other notification, and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. By continuing to access or use Wisconsin High School Forensic Association after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to have your Information collected, used and disclosed as described in the modified Policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.Last Updated August 25, 2020 (clarified purpose of third party services used; added Kinsta as web host and Arcstone AMO as membership management system; clarified that we do not provide non-personal demographic information outside our own, specific marketing purposes).Please contact us if you have any questions about this Policy.
